Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/vasudevan-dr-484b0b93 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Office

Research

Teaching

Languages

English

sanakrit

Tamil

Publications

67 international pulications in journals

vasudevan Dr

Registrar at Kalasalingam University

Virudhunagar, Tamil Nadu, India

Summary

I am basically a maths phd ,headed MCA dept of Kalasalingam from 1997 to 2003 .Then headed the IT dept for over ten years.During the same period i was the chief suprindetent of university exams for 6 years,Dean hostels for four years ,Dean admissions&dean placements for three years from 2011 to 2014 .then currently working as a Registrar from 2013.so for 14 students completed Phd under my guidance and i have the credit 67 international publications .i have been attached with this great A grade Kalasalingam university for more than 23 years.

Experience

Kalasalingam University Registrar September 2012 - Present

Kalasalingam University senier professor August 1992 - Present srivilliputtur,tamilnadu, India

Education

Madurai Kamaraj University
PhD, Mathematics and Computer Science · (1986 - 1992)

G.S.Hindu higher secondary school srivilliputtur sslc